Oh, I fear I may not survive this war reenactment.
I can't believe we're only
12 feet from the parking lot.
This is every bit as fun as the real Civil War.
Not the Civil War, Private.
We're reenacting the Sith-il War.
Sith? What the Hoth?
Enemy invaders!
Up in yonder sky!
I am Darth Stroyer.
Darth Stroyer? That's the
stupidest name I've ever heard.
Let's hear the rest.
Darth Trocious.
Darth Sploder.
Darth Urderer.
Darth It-head.
Company, attack!
Don't fire until you see
the greens of their eyes!
It saves on bullets.
I shall rip out your heart
and show it to you.
It is done.
The candle that burns twice
as bright burns half as long.
You're dead.
No, I'm just very old.
Whoa. That's good acting.
It's payback time,
Sploder.
Tell my mother to pick me up
outside Quiznos.
That's three dead.
Let's pick up the pace,
people.
At this point in
the actual war,
the death toll
was 98 million.
You humans
and your fragile organs.
One little stab
to the goo, and...
You're dead, Earth man.
Cruel fate, I'm dead.
They're putting me
in my Sunday suit
and shoving me
in a wooden box.
Now they're lowering me
into the cold, cold ground.
Hello,
here come the worms.
If you were really dead, you
wouldn't be laughing so hard.
Yeah, death's a big deal
to you flesh bags.
But in case you didn't notice, I'm a robot.
So? What if something heavy
fell on you, like a church?
You could still die.
Nuh-uh!
My wireless backup unit
saves a copy of me every day.
So, if my body gets killed,
big whoop,
I just download
into another body.
I'm immortal, baby.
What? Then how come
you always scream
so much when
you're in danger?
I never said I wasn't
a drama queen.
And the winner
of the war is...
Let me just cross-check
my tabulation here.
Factor in the corsages
for the widows...
Hurry up, you number-crunching
crumb-nuncher!
Everybody but me
is dying of old age!
Okay.
The winners, at a net cost of only
$12 per life cut tragically short,
our Sith Overlords!
Yeah!
Yes!
Hot diggity. I mean,
supreme diggity.
Good war,
good war, good war...
It may have been a fake war, but
my scuffed knee is all too real.
I've got pains in joints
I had removed a century ago.
Bender, bring me my soft
chair with the wheels on it.
Your wheelchair?
I don't need a wheelchair!
The one with the wheels!
Poor flimsy humans.
Don't you wish you were
flawless like me?
A towering inferno of
physical perfection?
I hate to pop your blimp-like
ego, but you are not perfect.
Am so.
Are not.
Is too!
Says who?
Says the only human whose
opinion I even remotely respect.
Inspector 5, the best inspector a kid could want.
The day I was built,
he looked me over,
probably with tears
of pride in his eyes,
and proclaimed
to all the world,
by means of this
scrap of paper,
that I was perfect and
infallible in every way.
Hey, Mr. Perfect,
you wet the chair.
Huh? It wasn't me. Must be some of
that urine you're all so proud of.
That's not urine.
It's oil.
Impossible. I'm triple-sealed
to prevent any chance of...
You call that
an ink defense?
Goodbye, friends.
What could have
caused the leak?
Excessive heat, on account of I'm so hot?
Alas, no.
Oh, Bender, I'm afraid it's
a symptom of a fatal defect.
Yeah, fatal, schmatal.
If I die, I can just
download my backup copy
into a new,
equally fabulous body.
That's just it. You can't! You
were built without a backup unit!
There's no backup
copy of me?
That's what I just said,
you mortal coil.
So, if I die...
You die.
Or as you put it...
Excuse me for a moment.
No!
I can't believe it!
I'm gonna die!
How much time does he have left, Professor?
Between a minute
and a billion years.
Well, at least you
can plan accordingly.
Dying sucks butt!
How do you living beings
cope with mortality?
Violent outbursts.
General sluttiness.
Thanks to denial,
I'm immortal.
Damn it, I'm supposed to be perfect!
Inspector 5 gave me
his blessing!
How could he bring me into
this world knowing I would die?
So you wish you
were never born, maybe?
Yes, anything less than immortality
is a complete waste of time!
Then suicide it is.
Step into my office. I'll
give you a nice Kevorking.
Not until I hunt down Inspector 5
and beat an explanation out of him!
I'm all for a good beating,
but you'll never find him.
Product inspectors
are bureaucrats,
faceless bean-counters
who blend into the woodwork.
I beg to differ.
Stinking bureaucrats.
I hate them!
Then again, you might be able to find Inspector 5
with the help of another
seasoned bureaucrat.
Hermes, old pal.
Old pal? 8.5 seconds ago,
you said you hated me.
Time heals all wounds.
You know what?
I will help you,
but only to prove I'm not just
a paper-pushing file jockey.
Will you be taking your
portable filing cabinet?
None of your beeswax.
I'll only be away an hour,
but I'm counting on you
to do the all-critical
filing in my absence.
Shall we review
alphabetical order?
A, B, C, D...
Get out of my office!
Yes, I'd like to request
a death certificate.
Sorry,
that's Building C.
The Central Bureaucracy maintains
records on all bureaucrats.
We should be able to
look up Inspector 5.
Application for
ingress approved.
And the other
potential entrant?
He's my pencil sharpener.
You betcha!
Proceed.
I maintain a cubicle here
for weekend getaways.
Wow. Until now, I thought
giant cubes were exciting.
I did like the part
where they screamed.
This is mine, right next to the center square.
Sorry, Hermes,
I drank all your Wite-Out.
Once I log in, I can access
Inspector 5's profile.
Damn it, it won't go on!
That's because
you're not me.
Hooray, it won't go on!
The bureaucra-scan
won't let anyone
but the assigned
bureaucrat log in.
Also, you have a rectangular mass in your colon.
That's a calculator.
I ate it to gain its power.
You locate Inspector 5 while I
slip into my ass-kicking feet.
Sweet file-not-found
of Puget Sound.
His record's been blanked.
Oh, man!
How am I gonna find some anonymous
guy I don't know anything about?
I recommend the men's room
at the TWA Terminal.
Okay, just file it
alphabetically.
A, B, C, D...
Well, this requires
a little extra thought.
I'm a natural.
The information we need will
be here, in the physical files.
Those bastards won't know
what leafed through them.
It's on.
No! This is impossible!
Quit blacking out
and look at this.
"Inspector 1, 2, 3, 4, 6".
There's no trace
of Inspector 5!
But 5's the one we want!
Maybe if I kicked the asses of
Inspector 2, plus Inspector 3...
Addition never
solved anything, man.
Let's cut our losses
and go home.
So I'm doomed to die,
and I'll never even get to
punch whoever's responsible?
What's the point?
Bender, no! Suicide isn't
necessarily the answer.
It's not a suicide booth, you
lard-ass. It's a phone booth.
They have phones
in booths now?
Finally, I don't have to
lug this cell phone around.
Who the hell is this?
How did you get this number?
Is this the robot company?
'Cause I have a complaint
about a defective robot.
His name is me!
A defective robot, you say?
Stay right there, dearie.
I'll have tech support
take care of you.
Well, things are
starting to look up.
Look up!
Who did you call?
Dial-a-bomb?
No, I just told the robot company I was defective.
You dumb cocktail shaker!
Mom won't allow a defective
product to tarnish her good name!
She'll kill you!
Big whoop. I'll just
download into a new...
Oh, right.
If I die, I die.
Speaking of which...
You're right. You're right. You're right.
That's what you get
for calling tech support.
I can't run anymore.
I'll have to skip.
Just a few more feet.
We have to get to that pile of dead bears by 7:38.
A pile of dead bears can only
mean one thing. But what?
It's the 7:38!
Jump!
Shoot!
Someone said shoot.
Well, we're boned.
No, we're not!
We just got to limbo.
But I'm not designed to bend
that low, not without limbo music.
That'll do it!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
We're gonna get fired.
Someone said fire.
We did it!
Twelve straight hours
of limbo.
I haven't done that
since my honeymoon.
Hermes, Hermes, remember that flock of bats?
I sure do.
That was fun.
Where are we?
I have no idea.
Hey, we're just a stone's throw from Tijuana.
See?
A rock has fallen here,
in the outskirts of Tijuana.
Is it within
the city limit?
I think, yes.
Told you.
Hey, you want to
celebrate our escape?
Maybe grab a shot of tequila and
take in a big-league cockfight?
Sure. No, wait.
I was built in Tijuana.
Maybe Inspector 5
still works there.
He better do some explaining before
I mash up some face guacamole.
He's Mexican, I'm Mexican.
Let me handle this.
Si!
Ouch-o!
Here are our passports,
visas,
and Homeland Security
permission slips,
notarized and starched.
Okay. I also would
have accepted a bribe.
Nice work, butterball.
You know,
I was in Italy last week.
My birthplace.
It's closed!
There's not even
a shrine to me.
With a gift shop,
selling piсatas of me!
End of the line, man.
Come on, we can still catch
a twi-night double cockfight.
No, wait! What's that
in the Mexican garbage?
Looks like
a half-eaten cheese diaper.
No, next to that.
A half-eaten
employee directory.
Inspector 5's home address!
His ass-ias is gracias!
Where are you hiding,
you coward?
Get out here and get
murdered like a man!
Bender, I'm afraid our search is
at an end. He's obviously long gone.
Oh, yeah?
Well, maybe this is
him in a costume!
I'm gonna squeeze you out of
there like Tijuana toothpaste!
Okay, Bender,
you're mortal.
And, okay,
Inspector 5 screwed up.
But that just makes the time you
have left all the more precious.
Do you really want to waste the rest of
your life in a bitter, homicidal rage?
No! Yes!
I don't know!
Why?
Why did he do this to me?
All I wanted was
a little quality control.
But he didn't care enough.
And now I'm gonna die!
I deserve better!
I'm Bender, damn it!
I'm Bender!
There, there, man.
It's gonna be okay.
You are Bender, which is something
Inspector 5 will never be.
You know what?
You're right.
He was just
a stupid bureaucrat.
A stupid,
paper-pushing bureaucrat.
A stupid I-dotting,
chair-squashing...
Oh.
No offense, Hermes.
You're not like that.
I mean, you're exactly
like that, but you're okay!
In fact, I'm putting you
on the do-not-kill list.
Come on, fellow mortal.
We're in Tijuana.
I want to live a little.
Help! I'm gonna die! That's
the opposite of what I want!
Quick, run out the back!
I'll hack into Inspector 5's
terminal and fake your death,
so they'll call
off the kill-bots.
You know that
terminal is unhackable!
I'm not leaving you,
and that's final!
Good luck, buddy.
Bender terminated.
Bender saved.
Cease fire.
Mom called off the attack.
Although I don't see how it's
her. Someone said, "Howitzer!"
Yeah!
All right! Yeah!
He did it!
And he's not looking back
at that cool explosion.
He's a hero!
What's happening?
The phone's been disconnected,
the ship's repossessed,
and Zoidberg's
getting overcooked!
This place never changes.
Leela, what in the name
of Jah happened?
Too much papers!
Not enough hiding plants!
It's all right.
This place just needs
a one-hour bureaucratizing.
You make it
look so easy.
I've smoked a lot
of paperwork in my day.
Hey, Bender,
did you ever find
that inspector guy
you were looking for?
Nah, but thanks
to this knucklehead,
I did find a new
outlook on life.
It's precious and sacred.
And you only get so many
millions of years on this Earth.
So, let's get brick-faced!
Little bird, little bird
Fly through my window
Find molasses candy
Through my window,
my sugar lump
Fly through my window,
Find molasses candy
Chickadee, chickadee
Fly through my window
Find molasses candy
Through my window,
my sugar lump
Fly through my window,
Find molasses candy